Dalton Walkley

1028 49th PL SW Everett, WA, 98203

<u>Daltonwalk@hotmail.com</u> 425-350-6741

Background

Self Employed since October 2017 performing computer troubleshooting and other tech oriented roles. Expert experience with hardware, software, firmware, and electronics troubleshooting, multiple versions of windows OS and Server environments, Mac OS, VMware, Active Directory, Microsoft Office. CompTIA ITF+ Certified, currently pursuing CompTIA A+ (Nov 1st).

JOB EXPERIENCE

Self Employed

October 2017 - Present

- Hardware, software and electronics troubleshooting.
- Computer consulting, assembly and installation.
- Windows 7,8,10 troubleshooting and installation, App troubleshooting.

Northwest Bloodworks, 2703 Oakes Ave, Everett, Wa, 98201 — Volunteer

June 2019 - Present

- Welcomed and monitored Blood donors.
- Ensured donors had a pleasurable experience with the organization.

Staples, 4920 Evergreen Way South, Everett, WA 98203 — *Tech Associate*

April 2021 - July 2021

- Assisted customers in computer troubleshooting, installation and repair.
- Assisted and guided customers on their tech needs and questions.

EDUCATION

Everett Community College, 2000 Tower St, Everett, WA 98201

Significant Classes: IT101 (Intro to info technology), IT111 (Networking Fundamentals), IT115 (Device and Mobility Fundamentals), IT145(Digital Forensics), IT161 (Computing Hardware/Tech), CJ203 (Info and Cyber Warfare), Engr101

Cascade High School, 801 E Casino Rd, Everett, WA 98203

College In High School Classes: Intro to Computer Science, Web Design, Graphic Design, AP Environmental Science, Chemistry

<u>Skills:</u> Proficient Experience in hardware, software, firmware and electronics troubleshooting. Understanding of multiple versions of Windows OS, Mac OS, Active Directory, and Microsoft Office. CompTIA ITF+ Certified, pursuing CompTIA A+ certification by November 1st.